WILHELMUS OLE JR



Zamboanga City.



09972976807



Wilhelmus.olejr@gmail.com

Github: github.com/wilhelmusolejr Portfolio: wilhelmusolejr.github.io

A passionate enthusiast of automation, design, and web development. With a natural curiosity for technology and a flair for innovation, and an innate sense of aesthetics, I carefully combine my passion for design with my expertise in web development, crafting visually stunning and user-friendly digital experiences.

Education

Bachelor of Science in <u>Computer Science</u> Western Mindanao State University Normal Road, Baliwasan, Zamboanga City August 2020 – Present

Professional Experience

A Mobile Assistive Application of Philippine Currency FULL STACK ANDROID DEVELOPER | July 2023 – Present

- Designed and to develop an android based application that identifies philippine currecy
- Used machine learning technology specifically image classfication
- Implemented text-to-speech technology

WMSU Online Consultation Clinic

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER | January 2023 - April 2023

- Designed and developed a web based system that allows patients to have an online consultation
- Implemented built-in tools for patients and rnds

Depression Level Prediction Using Machine Learning DATA ANALYST | November 2022 – November 2022

- Designed and developed a web based system that predicts the depression level of a person

- Get insights and explore the dataset
- Used supervised learning specifically classification

Skills

- Knowledgeable in HTML, CSS, and Kotlin.
- Confident in Javascript, PHP, and Python.
- Passionate in machine learning, automation, web and android application design, and web development.
- Experienced in SQL